(Ira Flatow:)This is Science Friday.
I'm Ira Flatow.
(Ira Flatow:)My guest today is responsible
for the discovery of the first
(Ira Flatow:)stable super-heavy element.
(Ira Flatow:)Welcome, Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
(Sheldon:)Thank you.
(Sheldon:)The university made me come here.
(Sheldon:)I didn't want to.
(Sheldon:)Big fan of the show.
(Ira:)So, I understand
that you actually discovered
(Ira:)this element by mistake.
(Sheldon:)Yes.
(Ira:)And some people in the science
community are calling it
"The Wonder Blunder."
(Sheldon:)Who?
Give me their names.
(Sheldon:)I bet it's Wolowitz.
(Ira:)It's just such a fascinating story.
(Ira:)Your calculations are way off,
(Ira:)but they find the element anyway.
(Ira:)It's like misreading
a treasure map
(Ira:)and still finding the treasure.
(Sheldon:)Can we talk
about something else?
(Sheldon:)Do you know that I yodel?
Thats interesting,
but this could be taking you
(Ira:)down the path
toward a Nobel Prize.
(Ira:)And in Chemistry, no less.
(Ira:)And wouldn't that be unusual?
(Ira:)Because you're a physicist.
(Sheldon:)Yes, yes, I'd be a physicist
with a Nobel in Chemistry.
(Sheldon:)Everyone laugh at the circus freak.
(Sheldon:)I don't need to sit
here and take this, Flatow.
(Sheldon:)It is because of bullies like you,
(Sheldon:)every day more and more Americans
(Sheldon:)are making the switch to television.
I (THEME SONG PLAYS) I